worldpropertychannel.com 2019-07-08

# Policies - WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL Global News Center

This Privacy Notice ("Privacy Notice") applies to WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL CORPORATION, its related entities, subsidiaries, whether or not wholly owned (herein known as " WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ ") and specifically, it outlines the types of information that WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ gathers about you ("User") while you are using the www.worldpropertyjournal.com website or any other related website that uses a WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ video service now or in the future. This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Terms of Use. Your use of the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Websites and any personal information you provide on the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Sites remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice and our Terms of Use.

WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ is firmly committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users and fostering consumer confidence in the Internet, Internet advertising and direct marketing. If you as a visitor choose to register or submit information to the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ via the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Website, you agree to the use of such data in accordance with this Privacy Notice. Please note that the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Website contains links to other websites, including, without limitation, websites maintained by WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ and their respective affiliates, which may not be governed by this Privacy Notice. Also note that WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ may use third parties to host all or portions of, or to assist in maintaining, the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Website.

Please note that because of the changing nature of privacy laws, consumer needs and our business, we may modify this Privacy Notice from time to time without the consent of users by providing advance notice on the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Website before implementing such modifications. We encourage you to review our Privacy Notice periodically to become aware of any changes that may have occurred. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Notice, or do not feel that your concerns have been addressed, please direct your questions to: Privacy@worldpropertyjournal.com.

Personally identifiable information submitted via the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Website is used only for limited purposes. For example, when you register to request future communications from WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™, the information you submit may be used to respond to you, to create a personal profile to facilitate further requests or inquiries, or to personalize your web site experience. In addition, the webmasters may, where necessary, use your information for various site related tasks.

WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ will only collect and use customer identifiable information for purposes of providing information by way of a WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ e-Newsletter, or to create and inform you of products and services that better meet your needs.

Such information will not otherwise be shared with third parties unless so disclosed at the point of collection. Personally identifiable information may be transmitted internationally to third parties for the purposes identified above. This may include transfer to countries without data protection rules similar to those in effect in your country of residence. By providing information to the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Website, you are consenting to such transfers.

Where appropriate, personally identifiable information may be disclosed to law enforcement, regulatory or other government agencies, or third parties where necessary or desirable to comply with legal or regulatory obligations or requests or for the purposes identified above. WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce the Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Website, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™, our Users or others. In all cases we will treat requests to access information or change information in accordance with applicable legal requirements.

You may at any time request to be removed from emails or other communications generated in response to your registration on the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Website. A customer may choose not to receive direct marketing communications from WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ in connection with WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ online services. Upon such choice, WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ (a) will not contact that customer directly with marketing messages about WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ online services, and (b) will not use customer identifiable information obtained from that customer's registration for or use of an online service to contact that customer with marketing messages about any WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ products or services. A customer may choose not to receive such messages by e-mail, by mail, or by telephone. You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Websites, in which case WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL&trad?; may not be able to provide certain services to you.

Please contact WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, your personal information, your consent, or your opt-in or opt-out choices via email to: Privacy@worldpropertyjournal.com.

When you access the Internet, the computers that host websites that you visit (Web servers) automatically receive some anonymous information ("Usage Data"). This "usage data" may include a record of which pages a Web browser has visited. WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ servers receive usage data when customers visit a WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Website. WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ may use usage data to provide advertising about goods and services that may be of interest to WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ customers, or to provide customized features and services. By using this Website, automatically consent to WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ using this information as specified herein.

WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ understands the importance of protecting children's privacy in the interactive online world. The WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Website is covered by this Privacy Notice and is not designed for or intentionally targeted at children 13 years of age or younger. It is not our WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL's policy to intentionally collect or maintain information about anyone under the age of 13.

WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ has in place reasonable commercial standards of technology and operational security designed to protect all personally identifiable information provided by visitors via the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Website from unauthorized third party access. WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

If WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ may post a notice on the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Websites if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing.

WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ and where applicable, its affiliate or advertisers may use various kinds of software devices to collect information about Internet use. Small files called "cookies" may be attached to your Web browser. These files identify your browser and save information so that websites can recognize you. You can set your browser to disable cookies, but some WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Websites (and other websites) may not work properly if you do this. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. To ensure that the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Websites are well managed and to facilitate improved navigation within it, cookies (small text files stored in a user's browser) or web beacons (electronic images that allow WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Websites to count visitors who have accesse? a particular page and to access certain cookies) are used on the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Website to collect aggregate data. Cookies and web beacons may be used to track information and identify categories of visitors by items such as IP address, domain, browser type and pages visited. In addition, on some websites, WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ and its advertisers may use small bits of code called "one-pixel gifs," or "clear gifs" embedded in some web pages, to make cookies more effective. Pixel tags also enables WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ to send email messages in a format that customers can read. And they tell us whether emails have been opened to assure that we're only sending messages that are of interest to our customers. This information may be used to analyze the number of visitors to different areas of the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Website.

WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ may use advertising companies to deliver ads on some WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Websites. The advertising companies may also receive some anonymous information about ad viewing by Internet users on WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Websites and other Internet sites. This information may be associated with a customer's web browser, but cannot be associated with a name or e-mail address without the customer's permission. (This means that advertising companies may know where your computer goes on the Internet, but they don't know who you are unless you tell them.) This Site may contain links to other independent third-party WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Websites ("Linked Sites"). These Linked Sites are provided solely as a convenience to our Users. Such Linked Sites are not under WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL's control, and WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ is not responsible for and does not endorse the content of such Linked Sites, including any information or materials contained on such Linked Sites.

WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Sites. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Sites. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.

WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, If you go to another website, including an advertiser's Website (for example by clicking on an ad), and request information or enter a contest, be aware that you may be authorizing another company, including an advertising company, to use information you supply. WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ is not responsible for these other websites, it is up to the User to read their privacy policies, and choose whether to let them collect information about what you do on the Internet. Please note that if an advertiser asks WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Sites, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but no? any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL's Privacy Notice does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Websites.

The services contained in this section enable WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.

Google Analytics (Google)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. ("Google"). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Application, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.

Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

For the opt-out: [tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing: USA - [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reports (Google)

Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reports, an extension to Google Analytics, is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. ("Google").

WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL uses Demographics and Interest Reports features to create reports about audience demographics and interest reports in order to understand our audience and to serve better content.

You can choose to opt-out of Google Analytics tracking by either changing Ad Settings on your browser or by installing Google Analytics' opt-out plugin on your browser.

WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL uses data gathered Google Analytics for internal company use only and does not in any circumstance share with external 3rd parties.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing: USA - [Privacy Policy ](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ will not sell, trade, or disclose to third parties any customer identifiable information derived from the registration for or use of an WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ online service \-- including customer names and addresses -- without the consent of the customer (except as required by subpoena, search warrant, or other legal process or in the case of imminent physical harm to the customer or others). When WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ uses other agents, contractors or companies to perform services on its behalf, WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ will ensure that the company protects your customer identifiable information consistent with this Notice. If WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ includes your name and any other customer identifiable information in a directory that WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ creates from information we receive as an online service provider, the company will give you the opportunity to have your information excluded from that directory. Business directories that WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ creates may, however, contain information obtained from other sources.

If you are a User accessing the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Websites from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Websites, which are governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Notice, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

In the event that WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

Any feedback you provide at this site shall be deemed to be non-confidential. WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ shall be free to use such information on an unrestricted basis.

This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the "effective date" detailed above. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ may only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Notice in effect when we received the personal information you provided. Your continued use of the WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ Websites constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions.

Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Notice or WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL's treatment of personal information by contacting us through this web site at: ? Privacy@worldpropertyjournal.com. When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL's policy to contact the complaining User regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between WORLD PROPERTY JOURNAL™ and an individual.
